Businesses and Professions Collection 0007.002.004
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Series I: Businesses Advertising-Laundry
  - Businesses/Discount/Amazing Stores/Dave's Deals, 1980s-1990s, 1994-1995; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    This file contains newspaper clippings about the closing of Amazing Stores and the opening of Dave's Deals.
    Lejfer, David, Retailer
  - Businesses/Entertainment, 1997; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    File contains newspaper clipping of the November 16, 1997 obituary of Beatrice Shulman.
    Shulman, Beatrice, b. 1896, d. 1997, Russia; Arts & Entertainment
  - Businesses/Financial Services, Accounting, Stock Brokerage, 1980s - 2000s; Newspaper clippings and photocopy; "See also" insert (Box 1)
    File contains newspaper clippings of articles announcing appointments, awards, and others news regarding financial services positions, including one photocopy from The Jewish Ledger. Includes a note to "see also" The Silverman Collection: Arthur Silverman Folder.
    Connecticut Bank and Trust. CBT.; Businesses -- Financial Services
  - Businesses/Food and Drink/Catering and Miscellaneous, undated; Newspaper clippings, flier, photocopies (Box 1)
    File contains newspaper clippings including an obituary and articles regarding catering services, contests, recipes, etc. Includes photocopies of advertisements from the 1930s and 1960s. Also includes a flier for a Gourmet Chanuka Cooking Class at the GHJCC.
    Businesses -- Bakeries; Businesses -- Catering
  - Businesses/Food and Drink/Fish/Bostonian Fishery, see also People/Cohen, Yale, 2000; Contains one newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    This file contains one newspaper article entitled "Fire Destroys Former City Fishmarket", about the fire which destroyed the Bostonian Fishery storefront, from The Hartford Courant, Monday, November 13, 2000.
    Bostonian Fishery.; Cohen, Yale, d. 1995; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Fishmarket; Park Street, Hartford, CT
  - Businesses/Food and Drink/Food Distributor/Hartford Provision Co./HPC Food Service, 1986-1991; Contains newspaper clipping of advertisement and HPC pamphlet. (Box 1)
    This file contains a newspaper clipping of a 1986 advertisement, as well as an informational pamphlet, for The Hartford Provision Company.
    Hartford Provision Co.. HPC.
  - Businesses/Food and Drink/Sun Ripe Orange Co. (Benjamin Apter), undated; Contains photocopy of one page of notes and one original envelope, both on Sun Ripe Orange Co. letterhead. (Box 1)
    This file contains a photocopy of a page of notes and calculations on Sun Ripe Orange Co. letterhead, as well as an original envelope from the company.
    The original document resides in "First Hebrew Ladies' Free Loan Assn. Collection/Financial Info./Worksheets".
    Sun Ripe Orange Co..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Fruit & Produce
  - Businesses/Framing, 2005; Contains one advertisement clipped from the Jewish Ledger. (Box 1)
    This file contains one advertisement for Marvin Janow's Custom Framing Depot, on New Park Ave in West Hartford, from the March 25, 2005 Jewish Ledger.
    Janow, Marvin; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Art & Framing
  - Businesses/Fuel Oil/Engineering Services Inc., Julius Feinberg, 1940s. see also Jewish War Veterans for information about Feinberg, 1940 - 1966; Contains three original envelopes on Julius Feinberg Oil Heating letterhead. Also contains photocopies of articles and photos. (Box 1)
    This file contains photocopies of newspaper articles and photos relating to Julius Feinberg, including a full-page for Nokol-Aetna Oil Burner. There are also three original envelopes on Julius Feinberg Oil Heating Co. letterhead.
    Originals of the photocopies reside in the Julius Feinberg Scrapbook file of the Jewish War Veterans collection.
    Feinberg, Julius, Engineer, d. 1966; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Fuel & Heating; Businesses -- Heating; Jewish War Veterans
  - Businesses/Fuel Oil and Gas, undated; Photocopies of articles and of 1904 envelope; 1937 magazine article; newspaper clippings; postcard advertisement (Box 1)
    The highlight of this file is a 1937 magazine article, "Toubman Keeps Pace With Changing Times," announcing the opening of a Hartford service station by Wm. Toubman & Sons Inc. Also contains a photocopied envelope postmarked 1904 on H. Fine letterhead; original and photocopied articles from the Hartford Courant, including obituaries and retirement announcements for regional fuel oil and gas industry members and advertisements; and a 1997 article discussing the influence of coal research on the computer industry.
    Fine, Harry; Greenspon, Bernard, d. 1993; Hoffman, Zalman, d. 1993; Isenberg, Charles S.; Lassow, Herman; Toubman, William; Wallet, Maurice; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Coal; Businesses -- Fuel & Heating
  - Businesses/Fuel Oil and Gas/American Coal Company, undated; Photocopies of fliers, articles, advertisements, photograph (Box 1)
    Photocopies of articles, photographs, advertisements, fliers and correspondence, from the Hartford Courant, the New Britain Herald, the News Weekly, the Hartford Times and other papers, concerning the American Coal Co. Inc. between 1936 and 1943. Highlights include an internal memo on scrap rubber collection, a bulletin entitled "Instruction Given for Oil Rationing" and a letter to American Coal customers urging customers to buy their winter coal a year early, as well as several invitations to the American Coal Co. annual stag parties.
    American Coal Co. Inc..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Coal; Businesses -- Fuel & Heating; Rations, War
  - Businesses/Furniture and Interior Design, 1918-1995; 1918 sales receipt; newspaper clippings; photocopies (Box 1)
    Highlights include a 1918 receipt for a sale made by Feinberg Bros. and a 1959 newspaper advertisement for Barney's from the Jewish Ledger. Also contains photocopies of newspaper articles, advertisements, and obituraries from the Hartford Courant and the Jewish Ledger and other ads and fliers for furniture stores in the region.
    Originals of full-size ad for Shoor Brothers and Hartford Courant article "The man whose voice you love to hate" (regarding Bob's Discount Furniture) located in Oversize/Business/Misc.
    Barney's Office Furniture. (Hartford); Feinberg Bros.. (Hartford); Kaufman, Robert "Bob", Store Owner; Koda, Paul, Cabinetmaker, Hungary; Lappen, Harry; Marholin's.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Furniture
  - Businesses/Furniture/Bob's Discount, 1997; Newspaper article (Box 1)
    Contains the June 1997 Hartfourd Courant article "They came out for Mr. 'Come on down'".
    Bob's Discount Furniture.; Kaufman, Robert "Bob", Store Owner; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Furniture
  - Businesses/Furniture/Marholin's, undated; Photocopies of newspaper articles (Box 1)
    Photocopies of newspaper articles, including oversize copies of the May 13, 1953 Hartford Times Financial News announcement of the grand opening of the new Marholin's location at 1177 Main Street.
    Marholin's.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Furniture
  - Businesses/Grocers/Burstein I. Meat Market, undated; Handwritten balance sheet from I. Burstein; I. Burstein. (Box 1)
    One undated, handwritten balance sheet from I. Burstein meat market.
    Business Receipts; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Meat Distributors
  - Businesses/Grocers/Copaco, 1967-2005; Newspaper clipping; photocopied article (Box 1)
    Contains a photocopy of a full-page advertisement for Copaco from the March 4, 1967 Hartford Times, as well as a 2005 newspaper article in the Hartford Courant announcing the sale of the company by the Bercowetz family.
    Bercowetz, Irving; Bercowetz, Kalmon; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Butcher; Businesses -- Meat Distributors
  - Businesses/Grocers/Crown Market, undated; Typewritten employee biographies; excerpt of the Federal Supplemen in re Crown Kosher Super Market, Inc. v. Gallagher; coupon circulars; photocopied and original newspaper articles, advertisements, etc. (Box 1)
    Folder contains typewritten biographies of partner/owners of Crown Market and materials which detail the history of this Kosher market in Hartford. Included are Crown Market coupon circulars and advertisements. Also folder contains many original and photocopied newspaper articles regarding Crown Market from the Hartford Courant, the Jewish Ledger, and the New York Times.
    Crown Market.; Smith, Alan, Store Owner; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery; Crown Market; Kosher; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Grocers/Dairy Mart, 1992-1995; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from the Hartford Courant regarding Charles Nirenberg's autobiography and his decision to forestall retirement.
    Dairy Mart Convenience Stores Inc..; Nirenberg, Charles; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Dairy; Businesses -- Grocery
  - Businesses/Grocers/Finest, 1991; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Folder contains newspaper article from the Ledger (04/04/1991) featuring story on the decision of the Finest super store in West Hartford to offer Kosher foods under rabbinical supervision.
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Grocers/Home Circle, undated; Hand-written narrative account (Box 1)
    File contains a handwritten narrative account of the founding of Home Circle Stores.
    Gershman, Charles; Home Circle Stores.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery
  - Businesses/Grocers/Ideal Meat Market, 1976-1981; Newspaper clippings; photocopies (Box 1)
    Newspaper articles and photocopies thereof concerning the Ideal Meat Market's closing in 1981.
    Ideal Meat Market.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Butcher; Businesses -- Grocery; Businesses -- Meat Distributors; Kosher; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Grocers/Kingswood Market, 2004; Newspaper article (Box 1)
    Folder contains newspaper feature article on the Kingswood Market (w/ color photos).
    Kingswood Market.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Delicatessen; Businesses -- Grocery; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Grocers/Lashin's Market, undated; Color and b&w photocopies (Box 1)
    Folder contains several photographs depicting owners, employees, and the location of Lashin's Market.
    Lashin's Market.; Lashin, Fannie; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery; Park Street, Hartford, CT
  - Businesses/Grocers/Manny's Famous Deli, 1980; Newspaper clippings w/ photos (Box 1)
    Folder contains newspaper articles honoring delicatessen owner Irving "Manny" Manekofsky.
    Manekofsky, Irving; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Delicatessen; Businesses -- Grocery
  - Businesses/Grocers/Mott's, 1986-1987; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Folder contains newspaper articles pertaining to Mott's Shoprite Supermarkets, including full page memorial for Sylvia Gottlieb, 1925-1986.
    Gottlieb, Sylvia, d. 1986; Mott's Shoprite Supermarkets Inc..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery
  - Businesses/Grocers/Preston Groceries, 1988; Newspaper clipping w/ color photo (Box 1)
    File contains Hartford Courant article (06/30/1988) publicizing the closing of Preston Grocery, on Franklin Avenue, and featuring the story of store owner, Abraham Cohen.
    Cohen, Abraham, Grocer; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery
  - Businesses/Grocers/Waldbaum's, 1997; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Hartford Kashrut Commision (HKC). (Hartford, CT); Waldbaum's.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Grocers/Wild Oats/Kosher Certification, 2000s, Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Jewish Ledger article (March 17. 2000) featuring a story on the natural food store, Wild Oats, and its dealings with the Hartford Kashrut Commission (HKC).
    Hartford Kashrut Commision (HKC). (Hartford, CT); Wild Oats.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Grocery; Kosher Products
  - Businesses/Hardware, 1984-1993; Newspaper clippings; photocopies (Box 1)
    Folder contains a series of newspaper articles pertaining to area hardware stores.
    Roth Hardware.; Strouse, Charles, Store owner; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Hardware
  - Businesses/Insurance, 1984-1995; Newspaper clippings; photocopies (Box 1)
    Business - Insurance; Insurance
  - Businesses/Investment/Venture Capital, 1987-1999; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Businesses -- Financial Services
  - Businesses/Jewelry, 1986-2003; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Folder contains series of newspaper articles pertaining to local independent and commercial jewelers.
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Jeweler
  - Businesses/Jewelry/Ernest Schall Jewelers, undated; cigarette lighter (Box 1)
    Businesses & Professions; Jeweler
  - Businesses/Judaica/Judaica Store (formerly Israel Gift Store), 1982-2003; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Folder contains a series of newspaper articles pertaining to the Hartford 'Israel Gift Shop'.
    Judaica Store. Israel Gift Store.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Gift Stores
  - Businesses/Judaica/Yehudit Gifts, 1985; Newspaper clippings w/ b&w photos (Box 1)
    Folder contains Jewish Ledger article (1985) featuring a story on the Yehudit Gift shop in West Hartford, CT.
    Yehudit Gifts.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Gift Stores
  - Businesses/Laundry/Mayflower Laundry and Drycleaning, 2003; Web printout (Box 1)
    Mayflower Laundry. (Hartford, CT); Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Laundry Services
- Series II: Businesses Manufacturing-Tobacco
  - Businesses/Manufacturing/Miscellaneous (includes Gerber), 1984-1998; Newspaper clippings (Box 2)
    Contains newspaper articles regarding Connecticut manufacturers, including several articles with the common theme of children succeeding their parents in the family business.
    David Kahn; Gerber, Murray A., President, Prototype & Plastic Mold; Irving Kahn; Jeffrey Kahn; Peter Youmans; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Manufacturing
  - Businesses/Manufacturing/Gerber Scientific, see also Gerber in People files, 1962-1997; Newspapers and newspaper clippings (Box 2)
    Contains newspaper articles about Gerber Scientific Incorporated (Gerber Scientific Instrument Company) and Prototype and Plastic Mold Company, including a 1962 Hartford Times article, "New Gerber Plotter Space Age Advance," and a 1997 Hartford Courant Business Weekly entitled "Gerber After Gerber".
    Gerber Scientific Inc..; Gerber, Joseph; Gerber, Murray A., President, Prototype & Plastic Mold; Prototype and Plastic Mold Co..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Manufacturing
  - Businesses/Miscellaneous, 1986-2011; Newspaper clippings, photocopies (Box 2)
    Contains miscellaneous newspaper articles regarding Connecticut businesses, from The Hartford Courant and the Jewish Ledger.
  - Businesses/Meat packing, see also Grocers, 1990; Newspaper clippings (Box 2)
    Donald Silpe; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Meat Distributors
  - Businesses/Mortuaries and Funeral Homes/, 1996-1999; Newspaper clippings (Box 2)
    Holtz, Herman; Leonard Holtz, Funeral director; Michael Weinstein; Morton Weinstein; Weinstein Mortuary.; Businesses & Professions -- Funeral Directors and Embalmers; Funeral services
  - Businesses/Mortuaries and Funeral Homes/Weinstein, 1982-2002; Newspaper clippings, photocopies (Box 2)
    Contains newspaper articles relating to the Weinstein Mortuary's 2002 court settlement, as well as advertisements, a Weinstein Mortuary calendar card and informational materials.
    Michael Weinstein; Morton Weinstein; Weinstein Mortuary.; Weinstein, Herman; Weinstein, Paul; Businesses & Professions -- Funeral Directors and Embalmers; Funeral services
  - Businesses/Newspapers/Connecticut Jewish Ledger, 1929-2005; newspaper clippings, photocopies, stationary, legal contract,; Gaster, Adele Diane (Box 2)
    File contains newspaper clippings from and about the Jewish Ledger's history, including anniversary notices, announcements of changes in ownership and articles about social events, in addition to original stationary on Jewish Ledger letterhead and business cards.
    Original stationary and business card from Berthold Gaster donated by Adele Gaster in December, 1992.
    Gaster, Berthold, Journalist/The Ledger, b.1926, Vienna; Jewish Ledger; Newspapers
  - Businesses/Notions and Sewing/D and R Blustein, closed 1983, Newspaper clipping (Box 2)
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Sewing and Notions
  - Businesses/Nursing Homes, 1993; Newspaper clipping (Box 2)
    Harold Moffie Jr.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Nursing Homes
  - Businesses/Parking, 1988-1995; Newspaper clippings, photocopies (Box 2)
    Lazowski, Alan
  - Businesses/Pharmacies, 1999-2012; Newspaper clipping; written narrative (Box 2)
    This file contains a photocopied, hand-written narrative about Euclid Pharmacy, written by David Cohen and Rena Cohen Citron, dated 7/12 without a year. Also contains newspaper clipping of Alec Goldin's obituary in the Hartford Courant from May 1999.
    Alec Goldin, Phamacist, d. 1999; Cohen, Hyman; Euclid Pharmacy.; Trinity Drug Store.; Businesses & Professions -- Pharmacist; Businesses -- Pharmacies
  - Businesses/Pharmacies/Baltimore Drug Store/Honigberg, Edward, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Printing and graphic arts/New England Typographic/Heller, Meyer, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Beckenstein, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Fish, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Friedman, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Hutensky/Bronson, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Konover see also Simon Konover and Family, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Levine, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Schonberger, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Simons and Steinberg, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Stich, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Real Estate Development/Udolf, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Avon Old Farm’s Inn, 2000s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Hearthstone, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Kravitz Family/Kay’s Fish Market, Our Favorite Place, Kay’s Too/Demery’s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Manny's Delicatessen, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Nanshe's, 1980s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Rosenthal, Richard/Max Restaurant Group, 1970s-2000s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Sage Allen/Talk of the Town, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Sam & Jack's (Crown Market), 1990s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Schmoozers, at JCC, 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Scholer's, 1950s-1990s, 1950-1999 (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/The Nosh, 1990s (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Restaurants/Top Nosh Deli, 1990s, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Scrap Metal, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Services/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Tobacco, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Tobacco/Hartman Tobacco Company, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Toys, undated (Box 2)
  - Businesses/Trucking/Edart, undated (Box 2)
- Series III: Colonial Realty
  - Businesses/Real Estate/Colonial Realty, undated (Box 3)
    General note
    After glamorous and highly publicized beginnings, Colonial Realty achieved notoriety in the late 1980s and 1990s for unethical and illegal business practices. The failure of Colonial Realty contributed to the economic decline of Hartford during that period. This collection consists of newspaper clippings that document the rise and fall of the company and its principals, Frank Shuch, Benjamin Sisti, William Calderoni, and Jonathan Googel.
    Real Estate
- Series IV: Professions
  - Professions/Accountants, undated (Box 4)
    Business & Professions -- Accountant
  - Professions/Architects, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Architects/ Berenson, Julius/ Architectural Examination Board of the State of Connecticut license, 1933 oversize drawer, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Arts, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Arts and Crafts, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Arts/Drama/Theater, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Arts/Drama/Film, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Arts/Drama/Television, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Authors, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Authors/Aromie, Nancy Slonim, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Collectors/Levy, Billie, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Dentists, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Educators, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Health/Holistic, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Legal, undated (Box 4)
  - Professions/Lawyers, Newspaper clippngs; Sorokin Sorokin Gross Hyde & Wiliams announcement card; Rubinstein, Reed D., Attorney, West Hartford
    Appleton, Pearl, d. 1994; Aronson, Stephen, Attorney; August, Moran, Lazorick and Shuster. (Avon, Simsbury); Banks, Morris, Attorney; Baram, David, Attorney; Bayer, Arnie, Attorney; Becker, Laura Gold, Attorney; Beizer, Arnold, Attorney; Berman and Sable.; Berman, Jonathan D., Attorney; Berman, Sable and Boatman.; Birnbaum, Robert J., Attorney; Blume, Daniel, Attorney; Borden, David M., Judge; Brandwein, David I.; Brick, Lawrence; Brown Raysman & Millstein.; Budd, Martin L., Attorney; Canter, Mark A., Attorney; Capstick, Daniel J., Attorney; Casey, Coleman, Attorney; Chorches, Martin, Attorney; Clayman, Markowitz, Litman & Tapper. (Bloomfield); Clayman, Markowitz, Pinney & Baram. (Bloomfield); Clayman, Martin A., Attorney; Cohn & Birnbaum. (Hartford); Convicer, Richard G., Attorney; Cooper, Andrew C., Attorney; Cox, Robert B., Attorney; Day, Berry & Howard.; Droney, John F., Jr., Attorney; Drucker, Leonard Murray, Attorney; Ebenstein & Ebenstein. (Hartford); Ebenstein, Douglas; Ebenstein, Norman; Edelson, Davida Schatz, Attorney, d. 1994, Hartford; Eisenberg, Deborah, Attorney, Glastonbury; Elkin, Sydney, Attorney; Eyges, Debra, Attorney; Feldman, Barry, Attorney; Fink, Everett F., Attorney, b. 1924 d. 1993; Flaschen, Evan D., Attorney; Gans, Jason, Attorney; Gerber, David, Attorney; Gillies, John J., Attorney; Ginsberg, Elliot A., Attorney; Gitlin, Richard, Attorney; Glassman, Kenneth Brian, Attorney; Globman, Benjamin, Attorney, d. 1991; Globman, Cooper and Marcus. (West Hartford); Goldberg, Arthur Abba, Attorney; Goldstein and Peck. (Bridgeport); Goldstein, David, Attorney, d. 1992, New Haven; Gould, Samuel, Attorney, d. 1994, Hartford; Greene, Barry D., Attorney; Grody, Jeffrey, Attorney; Gross, Howard I., Attorney; Harding, Preston F., Attorney; Harding, Sbarge, Svonkin and Droney, P.C.. (West Hartford); Haymond, John I., Attorney; Hebb & Gitlin.; Heiman, Maxwell, Judge, Unionville; Horwitch, Daniel B., Attorney; Hutensky, Allan; Jaffe, Seth Hillel, Attorney, West Hartford; Kagan, Eugene M., Attorney; Kallet, Mitchel E., Attorney; Katz, Melvin S., Attorney, d. 1997; Kershenbaum, Joseph, Attorney; Klein, Monte S., Attorney; Kleinman, Daniel E., Attorney; Kor, Robert, Attorney; Kosloff, Alan M., Attorney; Kostin, Dane R., Attorney; Krevolin, Feinstein and Freed. (Hartford); Kulick, Michael, Attorney; Lapuk, Marvin H., Attorney; Law offices of Lloyd Frauenglass. (Glastonbury); Lenore, Charles, Attorney; Lessne, Scott A., Attorney; Levin & D'Agostino.; Levin, Michael, Attorney; Levine, Ellen Schatz, Attorney; Levine, Kenneth J., Attorney; Levine, Tamara Kagan, Attorney; Levy, Coleman B., Attorney; Litman, Paul, Attorney; Lublin, Richard K., Attorney; Mahon, Brian T., Attorney; Mandell, Joel; Marder & Kallet. (Vernon); Marder, I. David, Attorney; Matos, Dan, Attorney, b. 1951; Miles, Michael, Attorney; Mizner, Neal, Attorney; Murtha Cullina Richter and Pinney.; Needleman, Marc N., Attorney; Oland, Mark, Attorney; Papermaster, Daniel, Attorney; Parker, Alan, Attorney; Perlstein, Mathew, Attorney; Pinney & Baram. (Bloomfield); Pinney, John, Attorney; Ribicoff & Kotkin.; Ribicoff, Abraham, Politician, U.S. Senator, 04/9/1910 - 02/22/1998, New Britian, CT; Robinson, Richard C., Attorney; Rose, John J.; Roth, David M., Attorney; Scharf, Roy Herbert, Attorney; Schatz & Schatz, Ribicoff & Kotkin. (Hartford); Schatz, Louis B., Attorney; Schatz, Nathan A., Attorney; Schulwolf, James C., Attorney; Schwartz, Lewis G., Attorney; Schwartz, Scott M., Attorney; Shipman & Goodwin. (Hartford); Shipman, Lawrence S., Attorney; Shipman, Mark S., Attorney; Simon, Melvin A., Attorney; Simon, Naomi, Attorney; Sorokin, Sorokin, Gross, Hyde & Williams, P.C.. (Hartford); Stoner, Gross, Chorches, Lapuk & Kleinman. (Farmington); Stroh, Charles, Attorney, Cattle breeder; Svonkin, Mark J., Attorney; Tapper, Joseph, Attorney; Tarlow, Jules S., Attorney; Tarlow, Levy & Droney, P.C..; Tarlow, Levy, Harding & Droney. (Farmington); Tarlow, Levy, Mandell and Kostin, P.C.. (Farmington); Upton, Peter N., Attorney; Waxman, Seth, Attorney, Hartford; Weinstein, Seltzer, DeNezzo, Swirsky and Kulick. (West Hartford); Widland, Michael L., Attorney; Businesses & Professions -- Attorney; Law